<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<!-- GiTS Cyberbrains HugsLib Update News-->
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Name="gitsCyberbrainsHLModUpdatesBase" Abstract="True">
		<modNameReadable>GiTS Cyberbrains</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>GiTS_Cyberbrains_HL</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3272114598</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="gitsCyberbrainsHLModUpdatesBase">
		<defName>GiTSCyberbrains_HL_1_0_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.0.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Another small patch based on user feedback rebalancing research progression and adding learning helper tutorials. Additionally, a non-steam download link also now exists on GitHub.

|Patch Notes:
* Added learning helper tutorials based on feedback. These skip lore unlike other descriptions and primary focus on usage in a simplified format.
* Updated melee damage factor values in CE patches.
* Updated Manifest.xml load rules for legacy users.
* Updated README.txt to include licenses.
* Lowered research project cost of central nervous cyberization, cyberbrain interfaces and the net by 200 each.
* Extreme cyberization research project cost raised.
* Closed Shell Syndrome rebalanced, focusing less on manipulation and more on learning/hacking ability.
* Fixed Cyberbrain Sclerosis sometimes not progressing if certain disease overhaul mods are also loaded.
* Fixed incorrect description of Cyberbrain Sclerosis.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="gitsCyberbrainsHLModUpdatesBase">
		<defName>GiTSCyberbrains_HL_1_0_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.0.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Small patch that finally backports cyberbrain abilities to 1.4 and adds graphic variations to cyberbrains as items! Minor balance tweaks and EPOE-Forked patch changes also made.

|Patch Notes:
* All cyberbrain abilities have been backported to 1.4 with Combat Extended support!
* New graphic variations of the cyberbrain exist for the basic, enhanced, specialized and extreme variants to make them visually distinguishable as items.
* Adjusted effects of OS40L Combat Network.
* Updated loading screen tips, added another five new loading screen tips.
* Texture path changes, please check this if you have written a texture patch for this mod!
* Pain Dampen and Pain Nullify cyberbrain ability toggles now only have a 1 second delay (previously 80 seconds).
* Pain Dampen ability now sets pain factor to 25% (was 20%).
* Basic cyberbrain now has access to Pain Dampen ability.
* Extreme cyberization now requires 3 days to adapt (previously 2).
* Cyberbrain Sclerosis now takes 30 days to reach full severity (previously 60 days).
* Minor fix to extreme cyberbrain adaptation phase stat changes.
* EPOE-Forked patch now adds brain surgery research requirement for the cyberbrain installation surgery itself.
* EPOE-Forked patch will now use MA-AI chips in all cyberbrain recipes.
* EPOE-Forked patch to replace cyberbrain graphics has been removed due to addition of new cyberbrain graphics. If it is requested back, I will readd it.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="gitsCyberbrainsHLModUpdatesBase">
		<defName>GiTSCyberbrains_HL_1_0_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.0.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Hotfix for incorrect values in some cyberbrains.

|Patch Notes:
* Fixed some incorrect statFactors values in some Hediffs.
* Fixed some incorrect statFactors values in Combat Extended patches.
* Minor changes to About.xml file content.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>